{
    "Questions" : [
        {
            "Comment": "THIS ISNT A REAL OBJECT. Since Json doesn't allow comments I need to make a fake object.",
            "Comment2": "Please create 17 more questions. 5 more easy, 6 medium, and 6 hard",
            "Comment3": "put 0 for easy, 1 for medium and 2 for hard",
            "Comment4": "Finally put all answers in caps"
        },
        {
            "id": 1,
            "question": "What is the dining hall name?",
            "answer": "PIERCE",
            "difficulty": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 2,
            "question": "What animal is the Stevens Mascot?",
            "answer": "DUCK",
            "difficulty": 0
        },
                {
            "id": 3,
            "question": "Does the president of Stevens live on campus?",
            "answer": "YES",
            "difficulty": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 4,
            "question": "Does Stevens have a bowling alley?",
            "answer": "YES",
            "difficulty": 0
        },
                {
            "id": 5,
            "question": "How many outdoor volleyball courts are there on campus?",
            "answer": "1",
            "difficulty": 0
        },
        {
            "id": 6,
            "question": "On what day of the week can you meal exchange on Washington?",
            "answer": "WEDNESDAY",
            "difficulty": 0
        },
            {
            "id": 7,
            "question": "How many restaurants accept meal exchanges on Washington Street?",
            "answer": "4",
            "difficulty": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 8,
            "question": "I pledge __ _____ that I have abided by the Stevens Honor System.",
            "answer": "MY HONOR",
            "difficulty": 1
        },
            {
            "id": 9,
            "question": "What is the maximum number of credits you can take per semester without overloading?",
            "answer": "20",
            "difficulty": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 10,
            "question": "What is the Stevens-created online platform for math problems called?",
            "answer": "GRADARIUS",
            "difficulty": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 11,
            "question": "Where do you go if you need help with writing and essays?",
            "answer": "WCC",
            "difficulty": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 12,
            "question": "What division is Stevens Institue of Technology, regarding athletics? It is D _?",
            "answer": "3",
            "difficulty": 1
        },
        {
            "id": 13,
            "question": "The 4+1 program is now called the _ _ _ (abbreviated)",
            "answer": "AMP",
            "difficulty": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 14,
            "question": "Under which building is there a garage?",
            "answer": "BABBIO",
            "difficulty": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 15,
            "question": "Which building has the fastest elevator?",
            "answer": "Howe",
            "difficulty": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 16,
            "question": "Most of the Stevens students are male or female?",
            "answer": "MALE",
            "difficulty": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 17,
            "question": "With what app can you change the music in Pierce Dining Hall?",
            "answer": "ROCKBOT",
            "difficulty": 2
        },
        {
            "id": 18,
            "question": "How many digits are Stevens ID numbers?",
            "answer": "8",
            "difficulty": 2
        }
    ]   
}
